(Sheldon:)Of course I understand. And who
are you to tell me about outer space?
Well, I'm the astrophysicist.
"Astro" means "space."
"Astro" means "star."
(Raj:)Let me just tell you,
if we were having this argument...
(Raj:)...in my native language,
I'd be kicking your butt.
(Sheldon:)English is your native language.
(Raj:)Okay, you got me there.
But you're wrong about this.
There's a fine line
between wrong and visionary.
(Sheldon:)Unfortunately,
you have to be a visionary to see it.
(Raj:)God, you think that every thought that
comes out of your head is pure gold.
(Raj:)Let me tell you,
some of those thoughts are pure caca.
(Sheldon:)Caca?
-It means "doo-doo."
-All right.
(Sheldon:)First of all, Dr. Koothrappali, when I first
proposed that you work with me--
Aha! So I am working with you?
(Sheldon:)In this context,
"with me" means "for me."
Oh. Yeah, well, in this context:
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
(Howard:)All right.
(Sheldon:)If I'm wrong, prove it.
(Penny:)Okay.